
> Configure project :
Fabric Loom: 1.9.2
Previous process has disowned the lock due to abrupt termination.
Found existing cache lock file (ACQUIRED_PREVIOUS_OWNER_DISOWNED), rebuilding loom cache. This may have been caused by a failed or canceled build.
:remapping 51 mods from modImplementation (java-api)
Mapping target name conflicts detected:
  METHODs com/cobblemon/mod/common/client/gui/pc/StorageSlot/[isSelected, net/minecraft/class_339/method_25367]()Z -> isSelected
There were unfixable conflicts.

[Incubating] Problems report is available at: file:///C:/GitHub/MirageEssentials/build/reports/problems/problems-report.html

Deprecated Gradle features were used in this build, making it incompatible with Gradle 10.

You can use '--warning-mode all' to show the individual deprecation warnings and determine if they come from your own scripts or plugins.

For more on this, please refer to https://docs.gradle.org/9.1.0/userguide/command_line_interface.html#sec:command_line_warnings in the Gradle documentation.
